EKE CHINONSO CHIZOBA

ADDRESS: 9, AZEEZ ADEPO STREET, ILE-EPO BUS STOP, IKOTUN-IDIMU ROAD, LAGOS

EMAIL: (preferred) chinonsoeke@gmail.com, ekechinonso@yahoo.com

WEBSITE: https://chinonsoeke.xyz MOBILE NUMBER: 07063944465

SUMMARY

A hardworking and straight forward individual, a quick learner with excellent listening and understanding skills. I believe in professionalism which makes me effectively talented and able to function adequately under pressure. I am a quick learner and can easily research and find what I need to learn and to do in order to complete a task. I am capable of working with people as well as individually to produce excellent results. A people person, very sociable and highly innovative.

WORK EXPERIENCE

August 2018 – Date: Web and Graphics Designer at Locus Group, Victoria Island.

Responsibilities

- Web management and update.
- Graphics and Campaign Designs
- Digital marketing and social media management
- Backend programming and support for Locus Group and its accompanying web assets.

June 2018 – August 2018: MTN Field Force Agent at Softcom, GRA, Ikeja.

Responsibilities

- Reviewed data entries received from the field force agents
- Accepted and rejected entries
- Supervised the Field Force Agents.

June 2017 - December 2017: Device Loading Executive at Softcom, GRA, Ikeja.

Responsibilities

- Ensured the devices were properly managed and in optimal condition.
- Installed applications to multiple brands of devices.
- Perform other duties assigned by the Supervisor.

January 2016 – July 2016: Federal Airports Authority of Nigeria, Ikeja Did my six (6) months SIWES (IT) in the organization. Worked in the ICT department

Responsibilities

- Fixed laptop and desktop issues.
- Formatted hard drives and reinstalled windows where necessary.
- Antivirus updates for the computers in the computer laboratory.

Perform other duties assigned by the Head of the Department.

January 2014 – April 2014: Covenant University, Ota, Ogun State. Participated in the Work study programme organized by the school Assistant to the head of the Computer Repairs & Maintenance dept.

Responsibilities

- Fixed laptop and desktop issues.
- Formatted hard drives and reinstalled windows where necessary.
- Antivirus updates for the computers in the computer laboratory.
- Perform other duties assigned by the Head of the Department.
- Went to other departments to assist with their computer challenges.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

2012 - 2018: Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.) Computer Engineering

• Covenant University, Ota, Ogun state.

Project Name: Development of a Fingerprint Recognition Based Attendance System **Project Summary:** The project was aimed at developing a student's attendance system, which effectively manages and monitors the attendance of students. The project was a windows application built using C# and SQL for the database. The project used a fingerprint device for scanning the student's finger.

2006 - 2012: WAEC

Ronik Comprehensive School, Ejigbo Lagos.

2000 - 2006: First School Leaving Certificate

• St. Pauls' Nursery and Primary School, Ikeja, Lagos

CERTIFICATES

IBM - Security Intelligence Analyst Mastery Award for Students

BIO-DATA

Sex: Male
Marital status: Single
Nationality: Nigerian

Date of Birth: 13th May 1996

SOFT SKILLS AND QUALITIES

- Strong interpersonal and excellent written and oral communication skills
- Ability to work individually or as part of a team, with little or no supervision
- Ability to cope and adapt well to new and varying work situations

- Strong adaptive ability to new task and issues
- Computer repairs and maintenance.
- Practical Application in
 - Back-end development
 - Front-end frameworks (Bootstrap), HTML, CSS.
 - Graphics Design using Adobe Illustrator, Figma.
 - JavaScript, JQuery
 - · Laravel, PHP
 - Microsoft Office Package
 - Mobile Application Development using Ionic Frame-work, React Native
 - MySQL
 - ReactJS, Redux
 - AdonisJS framework (NodeJS)
 - Motion Graphics using Adobe After Effects

RECENT WORKS

1. Web Application:

Site: https://www.tecky.com.ng

Description: Tecky is a website that connects freelancers (those who create websites, logo, business cards, Photoshop designs etc.) with clients who need their services.

Duration: 1 Month

Language used: HTML/CSS, Laravel for API, SQL, React JS & Redux for front-end

2. Website:

Site: https://www.dicio.com.ng

Description: A website that offers professional and reliable technical support for all computer and gadgets related problems throughout Lagos.

Duration: 3 Days

Language used: HTML/CSS, Laravel, SQL.

3. Web Application:

Site: https://www.yallaexpress.com

Description: A courier service website that does same day delivery for customers within Lagos, Nigeria.

Duration: 1 Month

Language Used: HTML/CSS, Laravel for API/backend, MySQL, React JS & Redux for frontend

4. Web Application:

Site: http://kainetix-sports.herokuapp.com

Description: A talent management and sports marketing specialist, taking advantage of the

abundance of talents in the African region

Duration: 1 Month

Language Used: HTML/CSS, Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap

HOBBIES/ INTERESTS

Playing computer games, playing tennis (lawn and table), listening to music, browsing.

REFERENCES

On request